

PROFILE

I had been worked with Tesco Lotus as an operation audit executive for 4 years which gain a lot of experience in retail business.

As an operation audit executive, I had learned store operation workflow both front office and back office.

Then, start working with Australian company as a medical tourism agency and had been coordinating with 4 main BDMS hospitals partnered including Bangkok, Pattaya and Phuket.

CONTACT

PHONE: +66 83 6456505

EMAIL: tnusita@gmail.com

ADDRESS: 98/11 Moo.4 Bangmaenang, Bangyai, Nonthaburi 11140

EDUCATION

Prince of Songkla University May 2011

Bachelor of Business Administration (International Program)

SKILLS

Good command of English
MS office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
Google sheets

NUSITA TANPHAN

WORK EXPERIENCES

Bangkok Representative Restored Beauty Getaways

Jan 2017 - Mar 2020

- Issue quotation, provide information for clients and managing clients data
- Responsible for database management for monthly report
- Assist international clients in arranging their medical holiday by coordinate with client/hospital/travel partners
- Build and manage relationship with key clients
- Assist international clients during their medical holiday in Bangkok

Team Lead - Operation Audit Executive Ek-Chai Distribution System Co., Ltd. (Tesco Lotus)

Jun 2016 - Dec 2016

- Plan and set audit schedule
- Auditing Tesco Lotus stores operation Large format (Extra, Hypermarket, Department and Talad Lotus)
- Collect issue, analyze the root cause of problem and inform problem found to the relevant department for further action
- Prepare audit report and summarize audit data

Operation Audit and Shrink Executive Ek-Chai Distribution System Co., Ltd. (Tesco Lotus)

Nov 2012 - May 2016

- Auditing Tesco Lotus stores operation Large format (Extra, Hypermarket, Department and Talad Lotus) and small format (Express), review shrinkage, monitor and investigate employees performance
- Collect issue analyze the root cause of problem and inform problem found to the relevant department for further action
- Prepare audit and shrinkage result reports
- Auditing special project required by manager and other related departments
- Operation audit checkpoints training for store operation team
- Review operation audit checkpoints and revise operation audit manual

Administration Officer Bangkok Airways Co., Ltd.

Sep 2011 - Oct 2012

- Manage related reports for internal usability
- Coordinate with other institutes including internal and external company to support the company activities
- Maintain and update pilots profile and qualifications record, control qualification of flight crew for transition training and promoting in rank
- Provide administrative support to all pilots